Taylor Scott

155 Vino Street, Palo Alto, CA 12545 ta y lor\$cott@ exam ple-CO m (125) 456-7890

Veteran personal and executive assistant with over 10 years experience supporting entrepreneurs and C-suite executives. Bilingual in Spanish and English and can carry on brief conversations in French, Support stress reduction in the workplace by maintaining a Mindfulness Instruction Certification.

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Psychology Sierra Nevada University, Incline Village, NV May 2006

Key Skills/Knowledge Areas

- Answering calls and emails
- Bilingual in Spanish and English
- Attention to detail
- Calendar management
- Proofreading
- Experience with plants/green houses

Certifications

- Certified Administrative
 Professional, International
 Association of Administrative
 Professionals, 2019
- ◆ Certified Mindfulness Instructor, 2017

Professional Experience

Personal/Executive Assistant

Enrique Lores (CEO Hewlett Packard, Inc.), Palo Alto, CA | May 2018 - Present

- Manage CEO's professional and personal calendar
- Coordinate global travel for executives and corporate groups
- Develop social media content for executive and monitor all his online accounts
- Proofread any customer-facing material and any internal documents signed by executive
- Pick up dry cleaning weekly and supervise housekeeping employees
- Reduced executive team stress levels through the implementation of brief daily meditations

Personal/Executive Assistant

Postmates Executive Team, San Francisco, CA | July 2014 - April 2018

- Drafted internal and external correspondence on behalf of the executive team
- Supervised seasonal office decoration and aided executive team members in decorating homes for investor parties
- Oversaw executive team schedules and company payroll
- Served as point of contact for customer inquiries and complaints

Personal Assistant

Dean E. Lucas, Zion Financial Analytics, Glendale, CA | October 2010-June 2014

- Prepared agendas, attended meetings, and transcribed correspondence
- Planned and executed events on behalf of the CEO
- Acted as office manager and maintained supply inventory
- Completed both business and personal online purchases for Zion
- Served as Liaison between executive and the public